Finding Aid for the Kay Sugahara Papers LSC.2354
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Business files, 1950-1988
  - REL financial statements, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - PRC - CCPIT, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Policy Study Group, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Philippines, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - REL, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 13-14)
  - Mexico, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Japan American Cultural Community Center, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Stig Host, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Nigeria, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 5-6)
  - Memos to Fairfield Directors, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Energy Decisions - Petromin, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Daehwa Industrial Inc., 1982 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Elf, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - OSS, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - VSS Guest List Dinner, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - First Annual Conference on Emerging Role of Asian Americans, 1983 October 22 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - USAI speech files, 1981-1983 (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
  - BOT files, 1981, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Fulbright files, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
  - White house - Linas Kojelis, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - William E. Brock letters, 1982-1983 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - BOT Certificates of Deposit, 1978-1981 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - University of Hawaii, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Matsunaga, 1979-1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Forum, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Joseph E. Curtis, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Lee Elder, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - John S. Erthien, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Fulbright Alumni Association files, 1978-1984 (Box 68, Folder 8-10)
  - Minority Business, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Mary Mochary, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Nisei Festival, 1983 August (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - American University, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Ray Cline - SAIS, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Motoo Shiina visit, 1984 June 10 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Craig Spence files, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3-8)
  - Alameda Project - Yukio Matsamoto, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - American Mercantile, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - American Mercantile Board Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 3-5)
  - Arco Tankers, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Bank of Tokyo, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Beatrice Foods, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Belize, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Citrus, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Coal, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Dr. Colish, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Peter Dent, 1976-1977 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Diplomatic Japan, 1981-1982 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Nakasone, 1979-1983 (Box 71, Folder 13-15)
  - Tojiro Nakabe, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Nigeria, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Mexico, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Fairfield-Maxwell articles, publications, photostats, 1974, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 4-5)
  - Tojiro Nakabe, 1980-1982 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Mondale Dinner - Tokyo, 1981 November 26 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous - KS, 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Shimanouchi, 1980-1982 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
  - Reefer Express Lines, 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 6-8)
  - Reefer Express documents, circa 1980s (Box 74, Folder 1-14)
  - Olympic International documents, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 15-20)
  - Thank you notes, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Toyota, 1980-1984 (Box 75, Folder 2-4)
  - US Windpower, Inc. brochures, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - W. Donovan Memo. Foundation Meeting, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
  - Chiyoda Chemical Engineering, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Conoco - Nicandros, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Drucker, Peter - articles, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Motoo Shiina luncheon, 1985 September 20 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Jim Amoss - Lykes, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Asian American Journalists - Tritia Toyota, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Cherry Hill commodities, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Yue-Sai Kan - Looking East TV, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Taro Aso, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Bank of Tokyo, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Benihana - Rocky Aoki, 1984 October (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Bermuda General, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Tommy Boggs, 1983 March (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - William Brock SIR, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Elaine Chao, 1986 May (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - William P. Clark Jr., National Security Advisor & Secy of Int., 1984 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Donovan Awards Dinner - Washington, 1983 May 24 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - HUB International - Jim Price, 1982-1983 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Assistant Secretary of State Holdridge, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Bank of Japan, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - IBJ - Masamune, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Culcon - DC, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Japan Center for Info., 1983 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - William J. Casey, 1983-1986 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Michael Kelly, Dept. of Commerce, 1984-1985 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Jushiro Kamiyama, Member of Parliment, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Margaret Liu - San Francisco, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Seely Lodwick, Asst. Secy Agriculture, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Assistant to President - Michael Deaver, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Atty General John Mitchell, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Neil Bush, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Vice President Bush, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - USIS American Embassy, Tokyo - David I. Hitchcock, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Mobil, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - William Morris Asst Commerce Secy., 1982 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Moriyuki Motono, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Takasaka, NHK - Interview, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Rose Ochi, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Papua, New Guinea, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Pierre Rinfret, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Senator Ribicoff, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Motoo Shiina - Policy Study Group, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - C. Spence Dinner, DC Gov. Hickel Alaska, 1985 March 11 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Ambassador Richard B. Stone, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - George Vasquez, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Textron - Beverly Dolan, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Fulbright - Board of Advisors, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 6-7)
  - Chianelli, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Citrus - Beef Import - Japan, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - William Kenney, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Japan Line - St. Marcet, 1984 October (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Matsunaga - Turbine Generator Info., 1984 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Gilbert Moore - Brooks Institute, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Olympic International, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - OPEC, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - G.T. Owens Mobil & golf, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - REL Board Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 5-17)
  - REL, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - REL B/D, 1985 March (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - J. Richard Ryan, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - National Committee for Quality Health Care Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Stockton Road/Aggen, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Sumitomo Corp., 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 6-7)
  - Taiyo Shoshen - Kenjiro Nakabe, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - George Vasquez, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Togo Tanaka, 1980-1982 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - VSS - Donovan Memorial, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - AMC, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 13-14)
  - B & C Associates, 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Joe Buchanan - IOC, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Fulbright Task Force files, 1983-1985 (Box 86, Folder 1-6)
  - Jean P. David - Zaire, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Frank J. Fahrenkopf, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Mushrooms Project - Fleming, 1984 December (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Prof. Richard Gordon, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Sec. of Interior - Donald Hodel, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Keidanren, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Mario Machado, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Prime Minister Nakasone, 1984-1985 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - H. Matsunaga, 1982-1985 (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
  - H. Matsunaga, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Tangerine Project - Wayne Newton, 1984-1986 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
  - Nigeria, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Ocean Thermal Energy, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Senator William J. Fulbright, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Jim Price, 1984-1986 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Khairy Hammoud, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Shimanouchi, 1983-1986 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Stephens Overseas - Vernon Weaver, 1983-1984 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Sudan, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Happy Sprite Christening, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Auto-Industrial Plant, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Diplomatic Japan, 1978-1980 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Diplomatic Washington, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - Directors Meetings, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Ecuador, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Elf, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Fairfield Goddard-Mann, 1979-1980 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Fairfield Industries, Inc., 1980 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Fairfield-Maxwell Services, Ltd., 1979 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Fairfield-Maxwell Ltd., 1980 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Great American Lines, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Houston - Waller, 1974-1977 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Japan Line, 1978-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Kashima Oil Co., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Kenney, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Kurio, 1978-1980 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Marine Data Network, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Mexico, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - MHTC, 1979-1980 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Mizota, George, 1972-1980 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Mobil Oil, 1978-1979 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Odyssey, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Olympic International - Azuma, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - OOC Auld/Conyers, 1974-1977 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Reefer Express Lines, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
  - SAJOC, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Sanwa Bank, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Sasebo, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Saudi Crude, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Seald-Sweet, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Seiba - Sekiya - Matsuda, 1975-1980 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Shaheen, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Skaarup Shipping, 1976-1979 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Sumitomo Corp., 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Sun World, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Taiyo Gyogyo, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Taiyo Shosen, 1977-1979 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Tankers, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Terra Marine - Baker, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Thank you notes, 1976-1979 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Toyota, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Vasquez, 1977
  - Nigeria documents, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 9-10)
  - Nigeria, 1974, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - B & C - Brown, Sparks, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Wm. J. Casey, 1986-1987 (Box 95, Folder 9-10)
  - Centenary United Methodist Church LA, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Frank W. Clark, former Navy Cdr. Colorado, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Frank J. Fahrenkopf Jr, 1986-1988 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Fahrenkopf Dinner Party - Tokyo, 1985 November 19 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Governor Hiramatsu, Oita Province, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - KS - President's Club Eagles, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Charles W. Greenleaf, Jr., 1988 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Kabir, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Loan by FML to David Fleming, 1986 June (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Kabir shares - trusts - gifts to grandchildren, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Fairfield West - BTS, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Keidanren, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Imayo Koguchi - M. Komatsu & Miyo Komatsu, 1977-1993 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Loans due FML & KS, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Tojiro Nakabe, Taiyo, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, Japan - diplomatic, 1983-1988 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Purina Taiyo - Ken Homma, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - REL - Byron M. Sugahara, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Walter Mondale, 1981-1983 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Keijiro Nakabe, 1986-1988 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Tomomitsu Ohba, V. Min. for Intl. Fin. MOF, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - VP George Bush letters, 1987-1988 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Kiichi Miyazawa, Min. of Finance, 1986-1987 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Amb. Yoshio Okawara, Wash. DC, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Oppenheimer - KS Retirement IRA, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Jack A. Rodgers, Charles Owens, 1986-1988 (Box 97, Folder 11-13)
  - Henry T. Shimanouchi, 1987-1988 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Jun Shiozaki, Min. of Economic Planning, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - David Stockman, Salomon Bros., 1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Oppenheimer - IRA rollover statements, 1987-1989 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Stocks KKG, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Stocks GNP commodities KKG, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Sumitomo, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Seisi Kato & Toyota, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Bryan & Diane Sugahara insurance, CG, 1986-1988 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Tokyo - US Embassy Min. Clark, Hitchcock, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - David B. Waller, White House Counsel, 1985-1988 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Aichi, Bush,Waller, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - KS interview Sankei Shinbun, 1982, 1983, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Avila Golf & C.C., 1982, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Bermuda Biological Research, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Kazuo Aichi, M.P., 1988 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Makoto Asabuki, 1984-1988 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Frank Carlucci, Secretary of Defense, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Chiyoda Corporation, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3-4)
  - Admiral William J. Crowe, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Donations & Loans - FML, KS Policy Letter, 1982 January 14 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Arthur P. Dudden, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Fairfield Industries - golden acquisition, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Frank J. Fahrenkopf, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - FML Directors file, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - David Fleming, 1986-1989 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Japanese American National Museum - Nancy Araki, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - E. Douglas Hamilton, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Japan Line, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Japex - Mr. Junnosuke Hidaka, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - JASSI - Midori Lederer, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Adnan Khashoggi, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Rev. Andrew Kuroda, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Raymond Levy, Renault Corp., 1987 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Matsunaga, RE & Wash. DC, 1986 June (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Matsunaga, Evergreen & Aquamarine, 1982 August, September (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Peru - Rick Lawless - WM. J. Casey, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Plimsoll Oil Corp. - Harmon Hoffman, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Ty Ralli - LeBoeuf, Lamb, Leiby, and McRae, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Steve Samela - Loan from KS - not used, returned, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - SPR - Strategic Petroleum Reserve, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Taiyo Financial Reports, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Tele-Japan, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - UCLA - Dean Weber, Chancellor Young, 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - USAI - Donations - KS & others, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - USAI - Highlights, 1982-1987 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - USAI - Conference, 1986 February (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - USAI - Senators' letters in support of PIP, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - USAI - Donations - KS, 1986-1987 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - University of Arkansas, Dean John Guilds, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Whittier College, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - James Ying, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - USAI - Board of Directors, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Wall Street Journal - Ed Pound, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - The White House, Ronald Reagan/Nancy, V.P. Bush, Howard Baker, 1983-1988 (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
  - Rick Lawless - CIA, 1986-1987 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Appleby, Spurling & Kempe, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Atwood Drilling, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Ashland Oil, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Bank of Tokyo, 1984-1988 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - FML Directors file, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7-8)
  - KS Directors files, 1983-1987 (Box 110, Folder 9-10)
  - Wataru Hiraizumi, Member of Parliament, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Hovermarine Pacific, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Tatsuko Iguchi, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - John Kidde, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - IBJ, 1986-1987 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Judge Yorka Linakis, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - H. Matsunaga - credit card file, 1982 December 27 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Nippon Credit, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Charles B. Owens, 1985-1989 (Box 111, Folder 12-13)
  - China Fund - S.L. Chen, 1986-1988 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - People's Republic of China, 1982-1987 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Sasebo letter, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Captain Nakamura affair, 1983 October (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Motoo Shiina, PSG, 1985-1987 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Taiyo Kobe Bank, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Toyota - Mr. S. Kato, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - USAI - Tribute to KS Conference, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - VSS 1980 and Donovan Foundation, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - T. Watanabe, 1982, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - KS - Olympic Intl. Ltd. Files, 1987-1988 (Box 112, Folder 10-13)
  - KS - OIL files, 1987-1988 (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
  - FML Directors files, 1973-1982 (Box 113, Folder 3-28)
  - FML Directors files, 1973-1987 (Box 114, Folder 1-14)
  - Fairfield Shareholders files, 1973-1987 (Box 115, Folder 1-5)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1984 September-December (Box 115, Folder 6-8)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1984 May-August (Box 116, Folder 1-5)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1983 August-1984 February (Box 117, Folder 1-5)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1983 July 1-1983 August 8, 1985 January 2-May 24 (Box 118, Folder 1-6)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1985 May 28-1985 December 5 (Box 119, Folder 1-9)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1985 December-1986 May (Box 120, Folder 1-5)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1986 June-1986 October (Box 121, Folder 1-5)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1986 November-1987 May (Box 122, Folder 1-7)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1987 June-1987 December (Box 123, Folder 1-7)
  - Kay Sugahara chronological files, 1988 January-1988 August (Box 124, Folder 1-8)
  - St. Marcet - JL - Yasui, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Yano Bermuda account, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Private info file, 1971 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Trusts - Keijiro N., 1966 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - REL desk file, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Komatsu - Bermuda Acct, 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Keijiro trust, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - FML brochure, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Profit sharing, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - FMLTD Agreement, 1963-1964 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Pomona Co., 1962 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Daitoh, FMLTD, HOP conf. papers, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Business cards collected by KS, undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Fairfield Japan posters, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - FM company directory, 1976 March (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - KS - FML History, 1974-1975 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - NYG chronological files, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 3-6)
  - NYG chronological files, 1973 (Box 157, Folder 1-3)
  - Tape letters, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 4-6)
  - Letters re: SSM and Conoco, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Toj. STN, 1964-1968 (Box 158, Folder 2-4)
  - PSK chronological files, 1965 (Box 158, Folder 5-9)
  - PSK chronological files, 1963-1964 (Box 159, Folder 1-4)
  - Komatsu tax, 1964 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Sasebo Heavy Industry, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Samarco, 1974-1975 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Philippines - Subic Bay, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Rigs, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Refrigerated Express Lines, 1974-1975 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - OSS, 1972-1975 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - O'Connell, 1973-1975 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Tojiro Nakabe, 1974-1975 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - President Nakabe's visit, 1975 October (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Mobil, 1974-1975 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Hishashi Matsunaga, 1975 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Mako art, 1976 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Libya, 1973-1975 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Komatsu, Mark, 1975 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Crude oil petroleum paper, undated (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Kanzaki paper, 1974-1975 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Kenkichi Nakabe, 1974-1975 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Abdulla Ali Kanoo, 1974-1975 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Japan Line, 1974-1975 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Hodson-Planning research, 1974-1975 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Hideca, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 5-6)
  - Fairfield, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Ex Com meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Bermuda Directors meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Directors meetings, 1975 (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Diplomatic - Washington, 1974-1975 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Diplomatic - Japan, 1974-1975 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Decorations, 1974-1975 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Iran Project, 1975 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - KS Washington trip, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 5-6)
  - OSS, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - Olympic International - Azuma, 1977-1978 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - Bills on oil pollution, 1977 (Box 195, Folder 14)
  - Y. Nakasone, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 15)
  - Rhode Island Fishing Group, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 16)
  - Shimanouchi, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Bills on oil divestiture, 1976 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - REL, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Profit sharing, 1973-1979 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Toyota Motors, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Tanker safety regulations, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Taiyo Gyogyo, 1977-1978 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - OSS VOSS, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Sunbelt Highway, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Sunbelt Dixie letters, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Sun World Pure Gold, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Sumitomo Shoji, 1976-1978 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - SBT regulations, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Saud Al-Sowayel, 1976-1978 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Seald-Sweet, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1976-1977 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - AMC weekly reports, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - American Bureau of Shipping, 1977-1980 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Tokyo, 1977-1980 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Bill Kenney expenses, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Diplomatic - Washington, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - American Mercantile, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Diplomatic - Washington White House dinner, 1980 October 21 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Luncheon for Sec. Duncan, 1979 October 10 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Echo Exploration Inc., 1979 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Elf/Socomet, 1977-1979 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Fairfield files, 1977-1979 (Box 199, Folder 4-6)
  - Foreign Exchange, 1976-1979 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Great American Lines, 1978-1979 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Japan, 1979 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - IBJ, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Joint Venture Agreement, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - HIC Inc., undated (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Kabir Enterprises, 1973-1979 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Komatsu, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - LQM, 1975-1978 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - MARDATA proposal, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - MMS owners binder, undated (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - MMS draft proposal, 1979 June (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Mahoud Elshazly, 1979 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Marine Management Systems, 1979 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Mexico, 1979 (Box 201, Folder 4)
- Series 2: Trip files, 1968-1988
  The trip files document Sugahara's travels related to FML, USIA, conferences, speeches, ceremonies, christenings, White House inaugurations, and vacation activities.
  - KS dinner with Joint COS Admiral Crowe at his home, 1987 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 30th Anniversary FML Dinner, 1987 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - White House Dinner, 1987 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - YS - NY Honolulu/SF, 1985 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - KS Tokyo, 1986 October 18-December 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - KS Washington & Bryn Mawr, PA, 1986 September 11-13 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - KS Tokyo trip, 1987 May 2-10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - St. Croix vacation, 1987 February 7-28 (Box 2, Folder 4)